blitware.com 2014-11-30

# Blitware Technology Inc. Privacy Policy

## Blitware Privacy Policy

Blitware.com is owned and operated by Blitware Technology Inc. ("Blitware"). Please read below for Blitware's privacy policy pertaining to the use of information collected from visitors who access this website. 

### Official Blitware Technology Inc. Privacy Policy

Our postal address is 1027 Pandora Ave., Victoria, B.C., V8V 3P6, Canada. We can be reached by postal mail, or via our customer support portal at <http://support.blitware.com/>. 

When you provide us your email address, we collect it and store it securely. Email address we collect are never rented, leased, or traded with a third party. If you supply us with your postal address on-line, you will only receive the information for which you provided us your address. 

If you provide us your email and you want to stop receiving email from us in the future, please let us know by writing to us at the above address, contacting the Blitware customer support portal, or clicking the "Unsubscribe" link in the email you received from us. Please allow 30 days for us to process your request. 

Blitware.com collects aggregate usage information on what pages our users access or visit. The aggregation of this usage data is strictly anonymous; no personally-identifiable information is stored. Aggregate information might include but is not limited to: countries that send visitors to our site, the amount of time the average user spends on our site, and which specific pages on our site attract the most traffic. 

The information we collect is used to improve the content of our Web page. We disclose this aggregate information when legally required to do so, at the request of governmental authorities conducting an investigation, to verify or enforce compliance with the policies governing our Website and applicable laws, or to protect against misuse or unauthorized use of our Website. 

Blitware.com uses cookies to record past activity at our site in order to provide better service when visitors return, and to customize Web page content based on visitors' browser type or other information that the visitor sends. 

We do not partner with or have special relationships with any ad server companies. Blitware.com does not host any advertisements from ad server companies on its website. 

Blitware has taken reasonable security precautions to protect our physical infrastructure against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our site. 

From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will post the policy changes to our Web site to notify you of these changes and we will use for these new purposes only data collected from the time of the policy change forward. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our Web site periodically. 

If you feel that our site is not following its stated information policy, you may contact us at the above address.
